                                    DAVID PEREZ


                                ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT





PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE                                           CONTACT

Administrative Assistant                                           •   (123) 456-7890
Sep 20XX — Present 1Redford & Sons, Chicago, IL
                                                                   ▪   david.perez@mail.com
  •   Schedule and coordinate meetings, appointments, and travel 
      arrangements for supervisors and managers                    •   47 W 13th St,
  •   Trained 2 administrative assistants during a period of           New York, NY 10011
      company expansion to ensure attention to detail and 
      adherence to company                                        SUMMARY
  •   Developed new filing and organizational practices, saving the 
      company $3,000 per year in contracted labor expenses        Administrative Assistant with 6+ 
  •   Maintain utmost discretion when dealing with sensitive topicyears of experience organizing 

Secretary                                                         presentations, preparing facility 
June 20XX — August 20XX Bright Spot Ltd. Boston, MA               reports, and maintaining the utmost 
                                                                  confidentiality. Possess a B.A. in 
  •   Type documents such as correspondence, drafts, memos, and 
      emails, and prepared 3 reports weekly for management        History and expertise in Microsoft 
  •   Opened, sorted, and distributed incoming messages           Excel. Looking to leverage my 
      and correspondence                                          knowledge and experience into a role 

  •   Purchased and maintained office suppled inventories, and    as Project Manager.
      always carefully adhered to budgeting practices

  •   Greeted visitors and helped them either find the appropriate 
      person or schedule an appointment                           KEY SKILLS

Secretary                                                          •   Microsoft Office
June 20XX — August 20XX 1Suntrust Financial. Chicago,              •   MailChimp

  •   Recorded, transcribed and distributed weekly meetings        •   HubSpot
  •   Answered upwards of 20 phone calls daily, taking             •   Google Workspace
      detailed messages                                            •   Problem Solving
  •   Arranged appointments and ensured executives arrived to 
      meetings with clients on time
                                                                  ADDITIONAL SKILLS

EDUCATION                                                          •   Spanish (Intermediate)
                                                                   •   Typing speed of 70 WPM
Bachelor of Arts in History GPA 3.5 
Graduated magna cum laude                                          •   Problem solving
Resume Genius University Chicago, IL                               •   Team leadership
May 20XX

