            RICHARD WILLIAMS
            Senior Financial Advisor

            (123) 456-7890 • 3665 Margaret Street, Houston, TX 47587 
            richard.williams@mail.com • linkedin.com/in/richard.williams


Financial Advisor with 7+ years of experience delivering financial/investment advisory services to high value  
clients. Proven success in managing multi-million dollar portfolios, driving profitability, and increasing ROI 
through skillful strategic planning, consulting, and financial advisory services.

Professional Experience
Senior Financial Advisor
WELLS FARGO ADVISORS, Houston, TX 
January 20XX - Present
 • Deliver financial advice to clients, proposing strategies to achieve short- and long-term objectives for 
   investments, insurance, business and estate planning with minimal risk
 • Develop, review, and optimize investment portfolios for 300+ high value clients with over $190M AUM 
   (Assets Under Management)
 • Ensure maximum client satisfaction by providing exceptional and personalized service, enhancing client 
   satisfaction ratings from 88% to 99.9% in less than 6 months

Financial Advisor
SUNTRUST INVESTMENT SERVICES, INC., New Orleans, LA 
January 20XX - January 20XX
 • Served as knowledgeable financial advisor to clients, managing an over S20.75M investment portfolio of 
   90+ individual and corporate clients
 • Devised and applied a new training and accountability program that increased productivity from #10 to 
   #3 in the region in less than 2 year period
 • Partnered with cross-functional teams in consulting with clients to provide asset management risk 
   strategy and mitigation, which increased AUM by 50%

Financial Advisor
MAVERICK CAPITAL MANAGEMENT, New Orleans, LA 
January 20XX - January 20XX
 • Served as the the primary point of contact for over 15 clients
 • Managed the portfolios of several major clients with over S8.5M in total assets

Education
Bachelor of Science in Business Administration (concentration: finance) Honors: cum laude (GPA: 3.7/4.0) 
RESUME GENIUS UNIVERSITY Baton Rouge, LA
May 20XX

Skills                     Additional Skills
 • Proficient in MS Office  • Additional Skill I

